[{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980918424,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":15216,"timeElapsed":553968},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980925576,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":7146,"timeElapsed":561121},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980931650,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":6065,"timeElapsed":567195},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980948319,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":16663,"timeElapsed":583864},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980953248,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":4921,"timeElapsed":588792},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980958827,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":5574,"timeElapsed":594372},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980962372,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":3538,"timeElapsed":597917},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980964005,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":1627,"timeElapsed":599549},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980968279,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":4268,"timeElapsed":603823},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980982592,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":12834,"timeElapsed":618137},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980986883,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":4281,"timeElapsed":622428},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980988835,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":1947,"timeElapsed":624380},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980991358,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2517,"timeElapsed":626903},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980993777,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2412,"timeElapsed":629322},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980995430,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":1646,"timeElapsed":630975},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980997059,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":1623,"timeElapsed":632604},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980998957,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":1894,"timeElapsed":634502},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981002669,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":3707,"timeElapsed":638214},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981011732,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"3","question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":7355,"timeElapsed":647277},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981014021,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"3","question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":2284,"timeElapsed":649566},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981021512,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"3","question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":7486,"timeElapsed":657056},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981022954,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"3","question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":1437,"timeElapsed":658499},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981024505,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"3","question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":1546,"timeElapsed":660050},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981026027,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"3","question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":1517,"timeElapsed":661572},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981028440,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"3","question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2406,"timeElapsed":663985},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981029963,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"3","question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":1517,"timeElapsed":665508},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981031549,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"3","question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":1581,"timeElapsed":667094},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981035917,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"36","question":"Describe a time you felt most full of joy.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":3186,"timeElapsed":671461},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981038023,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"36","question":"Describe a time you felt most full of joy.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2102,"timeElapsed":673568},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981039519,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"36","question":"Describe a time you felt most full of joy.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":1491,"timeElapsed":675064},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981041052,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"36","question":"Describe a time you felt most full of joy.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":1529,"timeElapsed":676597},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981042409,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"36","question":"Describe a time you felt most full of joy.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":1351,"timeElapsed":677954},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981043809,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"36","question":"Describe a time you felt most full of joy.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":1393,"timeElapsed":679354},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981046366,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"36","question":"Describe a time you felt most full of joy.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2550,"timeElapsed":681911},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981048586,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"36","question":"Describe a time you felt most full of joy.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2215,"timeElapsed":684130},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981050285,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"36","question":"Describe a time you felt most full of joy.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":1695,"timeElapsed":685830},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981054985,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":3655,"timeElapsed":690530},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981057493,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2503,"timeElapsed":693038},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981076509,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":19010,"timeElapsed":712054},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981079567,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3052,"timeElapsed":715112},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981080972,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":1401,"timeElapsed":716517},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981089772,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":8796,"timeElapsed":725317},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981091046,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":1269,"timeElapsed":726591},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981092333,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":1283,"timeElapsed":727878},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981094286,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":1948,"timeElapsed":729831},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981095486,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":1194,"timeElapsed":731031},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981101304,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":4966,"timeElapsed":736849},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981103755,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":2447,"timeElapsed":739299},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981105637,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":1878,"timeElapsed":741182},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981109006,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":3364,"timeElapsed":744551},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981121449,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":12439,"timeElapsed":756994},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981123308,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":1855,"timeElapsed":758853},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981124721,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":1406,"timeElapsed":760266},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981126069,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":1343,"timeElapsed":761614},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981128007,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":1934,"timeElapsed":763552},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981129725,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":1711,"timeElapsed":765270},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981143695,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":12878,"timeElapsed":779240},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981152209,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":8509,"timeElapsed":787754},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981160423,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":8206,"timeElapsed":795967},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981166374,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":5945,"timeElapsed":801919},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981168017,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":1637,"timeElapsed":803562},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981169724,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":1703,"timeElapsed":805269},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981171221,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":1492,"timeElapsed":806766},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981172363,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":1138,"timeElapsed":807908},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981173799,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":1431,"timeElapsed":809343},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981194401,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"227","question":"Do you have any unusual genetic traits (for example, cilantro tasting like soap, or particular allergies)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":19741,"timeElapsed":829945},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981195812,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"227","question":"Do you have any unusual genetic traits (for example, cilantro tasting like soap, or particular allergies)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":1405,"timeElapsed":831357},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981197373,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"227","question":"Do you have any unusual genetic traits (for example, cilantro tasting like soap, or particular allergies)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":1556,"timeElapsed":832918},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981198665,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"227","question":"Do you have any unusual genetic traits (for example, cilantro tasting like soap, or particular allergies)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":1286,"timeElapsed":834209},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981199997,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"227","question":"Do you have any unusual genetic traits (for example, cilantro tasting like soap, or particular allergies)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":1329,"timeElapsed":835542},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981202695,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"227","question":"Do you have any unusual genetic traits (for example, cilantro tasting like soap, or particular allergies)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2693,"timeElapsed":838240},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981204662,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"227","question":"Do you have any unusual genetic traits (for example, cilantro tasting like soap, or particular allergies)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":1960,"timeElapsed":840207},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981206258,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"227","question":"Do you have any unusual genetic traits (for example, cilantro tasting like soap, or particular allergies)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":1591,"timeElapsed":841803},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981207956,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"227","question":"Do you have any unusual genetic traits (for example, cilantro tasting like soap, or particular allergies)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":1692,"timeElapsed":843500},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981247902,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"24","question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":38252,"timeElapsed":883446},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981249217,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"24","question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":1310,"timeElapsed":884762},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981250340,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"24","question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":1120,"timeElapsed":885885},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981251960,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"24","question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":1613,"timeElapsed":887504},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981253486,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"24","question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":1520,"timeElapsed":889031},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981254796,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"24","question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":1306,"timeElapsed":890341},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981256034,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"24","question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":1234,"timeElapsed":891579},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981257712,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"24","question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":1673,"timeElapsed":893257},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981259362,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"24","question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":1645,"timeElapsed":894906},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981266412,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":6071,"timeElapsed":901957},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981268864,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":2448,"timeElapsed":904409},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981270331,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":1462,"timeElapsed":905876},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981271929,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":1592,"timeElapsed":907473},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981273244,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":1311,"timeElapsed":908789},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981283544,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":10295,"timeElapsed":919088},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981288878,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":5330,"timeElapsed":924423},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981297644,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":8761,"timeElapsed":933189},{"subjectID":"ar79a1b0pr","prolificID":"6724cc3dcff5f327298b4362","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23beb64bf78729eaba1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981299435,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":1785,"timeElapsed":934980}]